

K' Long C# .NET DEVELOPER

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

JQUERY, ANGULARIS

.NET MVC, WEB API, .NET WINFORM

GITHUB, RESTFUL API

INTERESTS

PROGRAMMING MUSIC

MIDI

AUDIO MIXING

READING

GAME

TECHNOLOGY

8 About me

I am majoring in software engineering.

I have some experiences with C#, ASP.NET MVC, .NET WEB API, Java Android I am interested around MIDI, Audio Processing and Music Producer.

Currently, I am focusing on web development with ASP.NET, ASP.NET CORE and I also have some experience working with this framework.

My goal in the next 3 years is to become a software developer specialized in .NET/.NET CORE framework.

10/10/1999

klong101099@gmail.com

Ho Chi Minh City

f https://www.facebook.com/longkelvin101099

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/long-kelvin-196a87181/

S live:.cid.a2e714512da2b6f4 https://longkelvin.github.io/

WORK EXPERIENCES -

.NET DEVELOPER

8/2021 - 12/2021

ELCA VN



Web application development based on .NET framework

.NET DEVELOPER

1/1/2021 - 30/6/2021

VIHAT TECHNOLOGY CO

Web application development based on .NET framework

EDUCATION -



SOFTWARE ENGINEER

2017 - PRESENT

VNUHCM - UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

GPA 7.35/10

PROJECTS -

COFFEESHOP_NETMVC

1/3/2022 - 1/6/2022

https://github.com/LongKelvin/CoffeeShopNetMVC C# .NET MVC, ANGULARJS



EZMIDI PIANO

1/9/2020 - 30/7/2021

https://github.com/LongKelvin/EzMidiPiano An Android Music App provide Midi and Synthesizer connection JAVA ANDROID, C++ JNI

ASSET MANAGEMENT

2019 - 2020

C# .NET CORE, ANGULAR 8
https://github.com/LongKelvin/ASPNET_CORE_QLST
Asset management for business

MINI SHOP MANAGEMENT APPLICATION

2019 - 2019

C# WINFORM, SQL SERVER https://github.com/LongKelvin/QLST-1 A small managerment app in C# Winform